experiencekissimmee.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy | Experience Kissimmee

Experience Kissimmee respects your privacy and values your trust. That’s why we’re committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains what personal information we collect, what we do with it, what we don’t do with it, and how we keep it safe - and how you can manage your consent or restrict data collection and processing. By using this site, you acknowledge the terms below.

We collect your data to tailor our website, emails, and other communications to your preferences and to the preferences of all experiencekissimmee.com visitors in general. While experiencekissimmee.com is still accessible and functional without the collection of your data, your experience on the site will be greatly enhanced upon your explicit consent of data collection and use. Note that we do not sell your personal data and we only share the data with partners for specific uses with your consent.

Experience Kissimmee is a private not-for-profit corporation funded primarily by the Tourist Development Tax. As a result, there is a substantial public interest in ensuring that the public funds are used in a responsible, effective manner. Anonymous data collection and statistical reporting is paramount in demonstrating accountable use of tax revenue.

You can update your consent preferences, request a copy of all your personal data from us, make corrections to your data stored in our systems, or request the complete removal of all your personal data from our systems by using the links at the bottom of this page.

We limit the use of your personal data to those purposes to which you agree and explicitly grant your consent. Your data helps us determine which content (text, imagery, video, and others) best suits your preferences. Sometimes the data is used in applications that compare your attributes to your peers in determining which content you would most likely prefer; other times your explicitly identified preferences are used in content curation. Additionally, anonymous and anonymized data is used for statistical purposes including general website and advertising performance reporting through various testing and analytics tools, which helps us improve the site and media for all users.

While some data and information are used exclusively within the channels they are collected (e.g. experiencekissimmee.com), we sometimes also match your data across multiple channels into a single profile. This allows us to communicate with you consistently across channels (e.g. email and advertising).

You can update your consent preferences, request a copy of all your personal data from us, make corrections to your data stored in our systems, or request the complete removal of all your personal data from our systems by using the links at the bottom of this page.

Who We Share Your Data With

We do not sell your personal data to any third parties. And while your data is stored in multiple locations (e.g. email engagement data is stored in our email marketing platform), it is accessible only to Experience Kissimmee, platform support staff (e.g. our email marketing platform technical service team for troubleshooting purposes), and contracted advertising, marketing, and communications agencies (all of which are located in the US, Canada, Mexico, Brazil, and the EU). Anonymous data (i.e. data without any personally identifiable information such as IP address, name, or email address) is made available in aggregate for partner advertising programs, which is why you may see co-branded banner ads with the Experience Kissimmee logo and the logo of one or more of our partners that directs to their website; however, a contracted agency manages these programs and does not provide direct access to the data for any third party or partner.

Note that data may be shared with legal authorities when required to do so by law.

You can update your consent preferences, request a copy of all your personal data from us, make corrections to your data stored in our systems, or request the complete removal of all your personal data from our systems by using the links at the bottom of this page.

We only collect the minimum amount of data necessary to deliver an optimal experience to you. Your data comes from a variety of sources upon your explicit consent, including visitation behavior on experiencekissimmee.com; engagement with our email messages; preferences stored in browser cookies; Experience Kissimmee advertisement engagement; and form data such as name, email address, mailing address, and preferences from forms on experiencekissimmee.com and our data partners. Our data partners append general technographic and demographic data to your information, which may include predicted values or ranges for household income, education level, home value, presence of children based on user location.

You can update your consent preferences, request a copy of all your personal data from us, make corrections to your data stored in our systems, or request the complete removal of all your personal data from our systems by using the links at the bottom of this page.

How We Ensure Your Data is Correct

Experience Kissimmee makes every effort to ensure that the data we collect and use is accurate by relying primarily upon actual behavior (e.g. which pages you view) and user-supplied information (e.g. the email address you enter on a form). Any extrapolated or third-party data sources used to enhance your profile are thoroughly vetted for high accuracy and reliability. Correct information is essential to delivering an enhanced experience to you, so we make available all your user data for your review and opportunity to rectify.

You can update your consent preferences, request a copy of all your personal data from us, make corrections to your data stored in our systems, or request the complete removal of all your personal data from our systems by using the links at the bottom of this page.

How Long We Keep Your Data

We only store your data for as long as necessary to deliver an enhanced experience to you. Because the typical vacation planning cycle can take several years from the first search to arrival in Kissimmee, we store anonymous and aggregate data for up to two years after your most recent interaction with experiencekissimmee.com or other Experience Kissimmee marketing activity. This storage term allows us to maintain a relevant conversation with you and it enables more accurate reporting on our end of the effectiveness of various marketing programs so we can continue to improve your experience and the experiences of users like you. However, if you opt in for ongoing communications, we store your data for as long as you remain an active subscriber to email, social media, or other direct digital communications channel.

Anonymous and anonymized data is stored indefinitely for statistical purposes including general website performance reporting through various testing and analytics tools, which helps us improve the site for all users, and for establishing the accountable use of public funds entrusted to Experience Kissimmee.

You can update your consent preferences, request a copy of all your personal data from us, make corrections to your data stored in our systems, or request the complete removal of all your personal data from our systems by using the links at the bottom of this page.

How We Keep Your Data Safe

While we work with various agencies and platforms to create a better experience for all our users, we strive to protect any personal data exchanged between Experience Kissimmee and those third parties. Personal data is only transmitted through secure means accessible only to authenticated authorized users, such as SFTP servers and cloud-based storage encrypted by SSL. This means that anyone outside of Experience Kissimmee that wishes to access personal data must represent a fully-vetted and contracted third-party and must log in to a secure system before gaining access. Additionally, if personal information like email addresses are used for advertisement targeting or other purposes with partners that do not offer a secure server-to-server connection, the data are first "hashed" using cryptographic encryption. Other personal data that cannot directly identify an individual but may still be sensitive, such as IP address, is anonymized through partial redaction.

You can update your consent preferences, request a copy of all your personal data from us, make corrections to your data stored in our systems, or request the complete removal of all your personal data from our systems by using the links at the bottom of this page.

Who You Can Contact About Your Data

If you still have questions about your data or Experience Kissimmee’s privacy compliance efforts, please use this form to contact us or reach out to our Data Protection Officer:

Jason Holic  
+1 407-569-4819 (direct)  
+1 800-333-5477 (toll-free)

We'll do our best to respond as quickly as possible.

You can update your consent preferences, request a copy of all your personal data from us, make corrections to your data stored in our systems, or request the complete removal of all your personal data from our systems by using the links at the bottom of this page.
